scs.co.uk 2012-12-30

# Privacy Policy | ScS Sofas

**When do we collect data?**

We can collect data on you from a variety of different sources these include.

  * When you register on our Website
  * When you speak to our customer services personnel
  * Via explicit data capture measures, for example by entering competitions and completing surveys
  * Via implicit data capture measures such as studying which pages you read the most and the use of cookies
  * In any of the above cases the data we collect could be personal data.

**What do we do with your personal information**

When you give us any personal data as indicated above, we may need to collect information about you to provide you with the services you expect then and in the future, and to communicate with you about special offers, sales and promotions. This information may include, but is not limited to, details such as your name, your address and your phone number.

Unless we have your express consent we will only disclose personal data to third parties if this is required for the purpose of completing your enquiry. This is of course subject to the proviso that we may disclose your data to certain permitted third parties, such as members of our own group, our own professional advisers who are bound by confidentiality codes, and when we are legally obliged to disclose your data.

By registering on our Website you consent to receive from us by e-mail, post or SMS message details of special offers, sales and promotions that we may think may be of interest to you. A. Share And Sons Ltd retains and uses your personal information to provide you with the best experience by providing you with a personalised service, and for internal administration and analysis.

For quality assurance and training reasons we may record calls you make to us.We do not sell, rent or trade your personal information to third parties for marketing purposes without your express consent. By becoming an A. Share And Sons Ltd customer you consent to the collection, storage and processing of your personal information.

**Cookies**

This Website uses cookies. A cookie is a small text file of which there are three types: Session cookies: These are used to maintain something called session state. If you consider your journey through the site to be a conversation with us and this cookie just reminds the site where we were in that conversation. These are required for the site to function but are not used in any way to identify you personally.

Permanent cookies: These store a few numbers on your hard drive. You can view them by looking in the cookies directory of your browser installation if you are interested. They last for a long time and each time you come to our site you send us a copy of them. We use them to identify you between visits. They are not required for the site to work but may enhance your experience. We do not store any personal data in these cookies, just a unique number that identifies you to us. 

Although you cannot block "session" cookies as they are required for our site to function correctly you can configure your Internet browser so that it can reject both "permanent" and "third party" cookies. How you do this will depend upon the Internet browser you use (for example, Internet Explorer 7, Firefox or Opera etc) and it is therefore impractical for us to detail here how you can reject those cookies. Please refer to the relevant Internet browser manufacturer's website where you should be able to receive all the information you need.

**Data**

In the UK we operate and are registered in accordance with applicable data protection legislation.

**Consent**

By disclosing your personal information to us using this Website or over the telephone, you consent to the collection, storage and processing of your personal information by A. Share And Sons Ltd in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy. Some information and e-mails sent to A. Share And Sons Ltd may be used as testimonials but no e-mail address or contact details will be displayed.

**Opt-Out Policy**

If you have registered on this Website you have the option to opt-out of receiving further information from us. To do that login to your account, click 'view details' and deselect the communication checkbox.

**Change / Modify Details**

You can amend your personal details by logging into your account and clicking 'edit details'.

**Contact**

To contact us click here.
